{
  "title": "Lesson 2.5 - Months of the Year",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Can you tell me what is the first month of the year?",
      "answer": "January. It’s January."
    },
    {
      "question": "Which month is the second month of the year?",
      "answer": "February. It’s February."
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the month after May?",
      "answer": "June. The month after May is June."
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the month after October?",
      "answer": "November. The month after October is November."
    },
    {
      "question": "Can you tell me the month after April?",
      "answer": "May. It’s May."
    },
    {
      "question": "Which month is the month after July?",
      "answer": "August. The month after July is August."
    },
    {
      "question": "What’s the month after November?",
      "answer": "December. The month after November is December."
    },
    {
      "question": "What’s the month after August?",
      "answer": "September. The month after August is September."
    },
    {
      "question": "Is your city very hot in August?",
      "answer": "Yes, it is. / No, it isn’t."
    },
    {
      "question": "Is your city very cold in May?",
      "answer": "Yes, it is. / No, it isn’t."
    },
    {
      "question": "Does your city snow in November?",
      "answer": "No, it doesn’t. / Yes, it does."
    },
    {
      "question": "When is Christmas?",
      "answer": "December 25th. / It’s on December 25th."
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you celebrate Christmas?",
      "answer": "Yes, I do. / No, I don’t."
    },
    {
      "question": "When is Chinese New Year this year?",
      "answer": "February 17th. / It’s on February 17th."
    }
  ]
}
